var q1 = [{"type": "tf", "question": "The purpose of Federal Information Security Management Act (FISMA) is to require all federal agencies to have an information security program", "correctAnswer": "t"}, {"type": "mc", "question": "The ___ mandates NIST standards for federal agencies.", "correctAnswer": "b", "answers": {"a": "CNSS", "b": "OMB", "c": "NIST", "d": "FISMA"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "FISMA mandates NIST to develop:", "correctAnswer": "e", "answers": {"a": "Federal Information Processing Standards (FIPS)", "b": "Security Publications (SPs)", "c": "CNSS Standards", "d": "DoDI Documents", "e": "A and B"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Which tier is the Authorizing Official (AO) responsible for?", "correctAnswer": "c", "answers": {"a": "Organization", "b": "Mission/Business Processes", "c": "System"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to provide guidance for implementing Risk Management Framework (RMF)?", "correctAnswer": "a", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to categorize the information system?", "correctAnswer": "e", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to assess the security controls of the information system?", "correctAnswer": "f", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to review and approve the information system?", "correctAnswer": "g", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to direct and oversee cybersecurity risk management?", "correctAnswer": "c", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to direct and coordinate the cybersecurity program on behalf of the CIO?", "correctAnswer": "d", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to support the information system owner and information owner?", "correctAnswer": "h", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}];
var q2 = [{"type": "mc", "question": "What is Step 1 of Risk Management Framework (RMF)?", "correctAnswer": "d", "answers": {"a": "Implement", "b": "Assess", "c": "Select", "d": "Categorize", "e": "Authorize", "f": "Monitor"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What is Confidentiality?", "correctAnswer": "a", "answers": {"a": "to prevent unauthorized disclosure of information", "b": "to prevent unauthorized modification or destruction of information", "c": "to prevent disruption of access to information"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What is Availability?", "correctAnswer": "c", "answers": {"a": "to prevent unauthorized disclosure of information", "b": "to prevent unauthorized modification or destruction of information", "c": "to prevent disruption of access to information"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What is Integrity?", "correctAnswer": "b", "answers": {"a": "to prevent unauthorized disclosure of information", "b": "to prevent unauthorized modification or destruction of information", "c": "to prevent disruption of access to information"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Changing grades by hacking into school networks is an example of a loss of", "correctAnswer": "b", "answers": {"a": "Confidentiality", "b": "Integrity", "c": "Availability"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Medical records being encrypted by ransomware is an example of a loss of", "correctAnswer": "c", "answers": {"a": "Confidentiality", "b": "Integrity", "c": "Availability"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Data breaches which expose customer credit card information are an example of a loss of", "correctAnswer": "a", "answers": {"a": "Confidentiality", "b": "Integrity", "c": "Availability"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What are the three possible Impact Levels in FIPS 199?", "correctAnswer": "a", "answers": {"a": "Low, Moderate, High", "b": "MAC I, MAC II, MAC III", "c": "Classified, Sensitive, Public"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What is the Impact Level for the information system if its information type is {(confidentiality, LOW), (integrity, HIGH), (availability, MODERATE)}?", "correctAnswer": "c", "answers": {"a": "LOW", "b": "MODERATE", "c": "HIGH"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What is the Impact Level for the information system if its information type is {(confidentiality, LOW), (integrity, LOW), (availability, MODERATE)}?", "correctAnswer": "b", "answers": {"a": "LOW", "b": "MODERATE", "c": "HIGH"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "What is the Impact Level for the information system if its information type is {(confidentiality, LOW), (integrity, LOW), (availability, LOW)}?", "correctAnswer": "a", "answers": {"a": "LOW", "b": "MODERATE", "c": "HIGH"}}];
var q3 = [{"type": "tf", "question": "In FIPS 200, there are 17 Families (security-related areas).", "correctAnswer": "t"}, {"type": "tf", "question": "Baselines should not be changed but applied as-is to the information system.", "correctAnswer": "f"}, {"type": "mc", "question": "A fence surrounding the building containing information systems would be an example of what type of control?", "correctAnswer": "a", "answers": {"a": "common", "b": "system", "c": "hybrid"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Selected security controls and rationale for tailoring are documented in the ____.", "correctAnswer": "b", "answers": {"a": "System Assessment Report (SAR)", "b": "System Security Plan (SSP)", "c": "System Assessment Plan (SAP)"}}];
var q4 = [{"type": "mc", "question": "Whose role is to assess the security controls of the information system?", "correctAnswer": "f", "answers": {"a": "TAG (Technical Advisory Group)", "b": "REF (Risk Executive Function)", "c": "CIO (Chief Information Officer)", "d": "SISO (Senior Information Security Officer)", "e": "ISO (Information System Owner) / IO (Information Owner)", "f": "SCA (Security Control Assessor)", "g": "AO (Authorizing Official)", "h": "ISSO (Information System Security Officer)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "The Security Assessment Plan (SAP) contains:", "correctAnswer": "d", "answers": {"a": "selected controls to be assessed", "b": "assessment procedures (ex: penetration tests)", "c": "schedule for assessments", "d": "all of the above"}}, {"type": "tf", "question": "The Security Assessment Report (SAR) contains the findings of the security assessments, and the SCA's recommendations.", "correctAnswer": "t"}, {"type": "tf", "question": "Found vulnerabilities are added to the Plan of Action and Milestones (POA&M), and deleted once they are fixed.", "correctAnswer": "f"}, {"type": "mc", "question": "The Security Authorization Package submitted to the Authorizing Official (AO) contains which of the following:", "correctAnswer": "d", "answers": {"a": "SSP", "b": "SAR", "c": "POA&M", "d": "all of the above"}}];
var q5 = [{"type": "mc", "question": "Which is not an authorization decision option in RMF?", "correctAnswer": "c", "answers": {"a": "Approval to Operate (ATO)", "b": "Interim Approval to Test (IATT)", "c": "Interim Authorization to Operate (IATO)", "d": "Denial of Approval to Operate (DATO)"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "How long can an Approval to Operate (ATO) last?", "correctAnswer": "d", "answers": {"a": "up to 180 days", "b": "up to 1 year", "c": "up to 2 years", "d": "up to 3 years"}}, {"type": "mc", "question": "Which step is in RMF but not in DIACAP?", "correctAnswer": "f", "answers": {"a": "Implement", "b": "Assess", "c": "Select", "d": "Categorize", "e": "Authorize", "f": "Continuous Monitor"}}, {"type": "tf", "question": "RMF's A&A process stands for Assessment & Authorization.", "correctAnswer": "t"}, {"type": "tf", "question": "DIACAP's C&A stands for Certification & Accreditation.", "correctAnswer": "t"}, {"type": "mc", "question": "RMF's advantages over DIACAP include:", "correctAnswer": "d", "answers": {"a": "stronger integration into the System Development Life Cycle", "b": "standards for all entire Federal agencies and contractors", "c": "common terminology and standard controls enable reciprocity between agencies", "d": "all of the above"}}];
